ABOUT

I'm a hungry creative with over two years of experience in advertising. I've successfully grown multiple brands through quality and purposeful designs. When I'm not indulging in gourmet donuts, I'm expanding my skills into web, video, and photography. I continually strive to grow through creative collaboration and exploration.

Email | MJKoruim@gmail.com Cell Phone | (954) 632-8112 Portfolio | morgankourim.com

EDUCATION

University of Central Florida Bachelor of Fine Arts Emerging Media - Graphic Design Summa Cum Laude 2012 - 2016

SKILLS

Adobe Creative Suite

InDesign, Illustrator, Photoshop Lightroom, Dreamweaver

Microsoft Office

Word, Powerpoint, Excel

Web and Programming

WordPress, Basic HTML / CSS

Professional

Organization, Time Management Project Management

EXPERIENCE

Production Artist | July 2016 - August 2017
OGK Creative | Delray Beach, Florida
Helped establish brand identities through marketing efforts by
maintaining, editing and creating collateral for a diverse clientele.

Design Intern | January 2016 - April 2016 REMIXED | Orlando, Florida Assisted in creating marketing collateral and building brand identities under the creative direction of the founding partners.

UCF SVAD Designer | January 2015 - December 2015 Center for Entrepreneurial Leadership | Orlando, Florida Collaborated with designers to provide students with design services to help grow their entrepreneurial endeavors.

Design and Marketing Intern | May 2015 - August 2015 Koncept Events | Fort Lauderdale, Florida Increased clientele and promoted the brand through multiple channels under the guidance of the Director of Marketing.

Graphic and Web Design Intern | May 2014 - August 2014 iGreen Marketing | Coconut Creek, Florida Built and maintained brand identity for clients through print and web design under the leadership of the Senior Designer.

HONORS AND AWARDS

UCF Scholar's Award | 2013 - 2015 Academic Scholarship

UCF President's Honor Roll 2014 - 2015 Maintained a 4.0 GPA

3rd in Video Production | 2012 Business Professionals of America National Leadership Conference

1st in Graphic Design | 2011 Business Professionals of America Florida State Leadership Conference

^{*}References available upon request